A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- Rollins, E.M. "Evaluation of multimedia environmental transport models for use in the Yucca Mountain environmental impact statement no-action alternative." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Rollins, E.M. "Final bounding impacts resulting from contaminated floodplains." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Shipers, R.L. and Harlan, C.P. "Background information for the development of a low-level waste performance assessment methodology, vol. 2: Assessment of relative significance of migration and exposure pathways." Sandia National Laboratories. NUREG/CR-5453, SAND89-2509. (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Sinkowski, D.S. "Population affected from continued storage and degradation of spent nuclear fuels and high-level waste." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. 1 of 2. (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Sinkowski, D.S. "Population affected from continued storage and degradation of spent nuclear fuels and high-level waste." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. 2 of 2. (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Toblin, A.L. "Final all water pathway analysis from continued storage and degradation of spent nuclear fuel and high-level waste materials under loss of institutional control." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Toblin, A.L. "Near field groundwater transport and gardener dose consequence." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 83, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Floodplain assessment of surface-based investigations at the Yucca Mountain site, Nye County, Nevada." YMP/91-11. (Box 83, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Floodplain assessment of characterization activities at the Yucca Mountain site, Nye County, Nevada." YMP/92-30. (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Fish and Wildlife Service. "Death Valley Nevada 1:250,000-scale wetland map of national wetlands inventory." (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Steen, D.C., Hall, D.B., Greger, P.D. et al. "Distribution of the chuckwalla, western burrowing owl, and six bat species on the Nevada test site." Bechdel Corporation. DOE/NV/11718-149. (Box 83, Folder 6)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Bats of Yucca Mountain, Nevada." (Box 83, Folder 7)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Species composition and abundance of reptile populations in selected habitats at Yucca Mountain, Nevada, with annotated checklist." (Box 83, Folder 8)
- U.S. Geological Survey. "Busted Butte Quadrangle, Nevada-Nye County, 7.5-minute series topographic map." (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Lincoln County/City of Caliente. "Bibliography of sponsored research 1985-1995: Repository oversight and impact alleviation planning program." (Box 83, Folder 10)
- University of Nevada, Reno. "Economic impact model for Lincoln County." Technical report UCED 94-08. (Box 83, Folder 11)
- University of Nevada, Reno. "Lincoln County economic impact model." (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Sathisan, S.K., Madhavapeddi, K. Lim, S. et al. "Risk analysis for spent nuclear fuel transportation through Lincoln County Volume I: Rail shipments, volume IIA: highway shipments, volume IIB: Technical appendix." Transportation Research Center, University of Nevada, Las Vegas. (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Clark County Department of Comprehensive Planning, Nuclear Waste Division. "Transmittal of information on the draft Yucca Mountain environmental impact statement." (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Himmelberger, J.J. (CENTED/ETS Program), Ogneva-Himmelberger, Y.A. (IDRISI Project, George Perkins Marsh Institute) and Intertech Services Corporation. "Tourism impacts of three mile island and other adverse events: Implications for Lincoln county and other rural counties bisected by radioactive wastes intended for Yucca Mountain." (Box 83, Folder 15)
- University of Nevada, Reno. "Economic trends and development strategies for Lincoln County." (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Center for Economic Development University of Nevada, Reno. "Lincoln County/City of Caliente: Industrial fiscal impact model user's manual for Lincoln County." (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Intertech Services Corp. "Lincoln County/City of Caliente: Lincoln County nuclear waste management program: Impact assessment and alleviation planning system description and status report 1985-1996." (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Intertech Services Corp. "The 1998 Lincoln County labor market survey and update." (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Board of Lincoln County Commissioners and City of Caliente. "Repository EIS scoping report: Issues identified by Lincoln County and the City of Caliente needing to be addressed within the repository environmental impact statement." (Box 84, Folder 4)
- University of Nevada, Reno. "Retail sales analysis for Lincoln County, Nevada." (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Resource Concepts, Inc. "Lincoln County/City of Caliente emergency preparedness inventory and analysis." (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Harris, T.R., Darden, T., Borden, G.W. et al. "Social accounting interregional model for Lincoln County." Technical report UCED 98/99-01. University of Nevada, Reno. (Box 84, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Preapproval draft environmental assessment for a proposed alternative energy generation facility at the Nevada test site." DOE/EA-1370. (Box 84, Folder 8)
- White Pine County Nuclear Waste Project Office. "[White Pine County nuclear waste project supplemental information]." (Box 84, Folder 9)
- U.S. Bureau of Mines. "Mineral facts and problems." Bulletin 675. (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Parker, G.J. "[Baseline change proposal (BCP-00-99-0009, Rev 0: Incorporate license application design selection (LADS) enhanced design alternative (EDA) II into the YMSCO project baseline. Memorandum to L. Barrett]." (Box 84, Folder 11)
- McKenzie, D.G. III. "[Environmental impact statement (EIS) supplemental information. Letter to K.J. Skipper, DOE]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Griffith, G.W. "[Repository surface design engineering files letter report - MGR solar power system (revision 2). Letter to D. Kane and K. Skipper, DOE]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Gambogi, J. "Titanium." From Minerals Yearbook: Metals and Minerals 1997 vol. 1. (Box 84, Folder 14)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Total system performance assessment for the site recommendation." TDR-WIS-PA-000001 REV 00 ICN 01. Ch. 1-2. (Box 85, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Total system performance assessment for the site recommendation." TDR-WIS-PA-000001 REV 00 ICN 0. Ch. 3. (Box 85, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Total system performance assessment for the site recommendation." TDR-WIS-PA-000001 REV 00 ICN 0. Ch. 4-7. (Box 85, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Total system performance assessment for the site recommendation." TDR-WIS-PA-000001 REV 00 ICN 01. Appendices. (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Buck, P.E., Amick, D.S. and Hartwell, W.T. "The Midway Valley Site (26NY4759): A prehistoric lithic quarry near Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." Quaternary Sciences Center, Desert Research Institute. (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Buck, P.E., Hartwell, W.T., Haynes, G. et al. "Investigations at two early Holocene sites near Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." Quaternary Sciences Center, Desert Research Institute. (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Cohon, J.L. "[Comments of Nuclear Waste Technical Review Board on meeting of August 1 and 2, 2000]." (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Ventilation system radon review." CAL-SSM-NU-000002 REV 00. (Box 86, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "License application design selection report." B00000000-01717-4600-00123 REV 01 ICN 01. (Box 86, Folder 5)
- "Yucca Mountain final environmental impact statement reference information." (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Aaberg, R.L. and Baker, D.A. "Dose commitments due to radioactive releases from nuclear power plant sites in 1992." Pacific Northwest Laboratory, Battelle Memorial Institute. NUREG/CR-2850 PNL-4221. Vol. 14. (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Association of American Railroads. "1998 field manual of the A.A.R. interchange rules [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Association of American Railroads. "Circular no. OT-55-C (CPC-1108): Recommended railroad operating practices for transportation of hazardous materials." (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Ahmer, D. "Cost estimate for the heavy haul truck transport design." EIS: AR-TR-80036. (Box 87, Folder 3)
- American Indian Ethnography Team. "Preliminary cultural assessment of Wildhorse Spring and the Willow Springs Complex on and near the Nellis Air Force Range [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Albin, A.L., Singleton, W.L. Moyer, T.C. et al. "Geology of the main drift - station 28+00 to 55+00, exploratory studies facility Yucca Mountain project, Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Bureau of Reclamation and U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 87, Folder 5)
- American National Standards Institute, Inc. "American national standard for truckload quantities of radioactive materials - carrier and shipper responsibilities and emergency response procedures for highway transportation accidents." ANSI N14.27-1986 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- American Railway Engineering Association. "Track: Volume 1 of the manual for railway engineering [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Arenaz, M.R. "[DOE SNF data used in the final environmental impact statement (EIS) (EM-NP-01-004). Memorandum to S.J. Brocoum (Office of Licensing & Regulatory Compliance)]." (Department of Energy, National Spent Nuclear Fuel Program. (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Armstrong, R.L. "Sevier orogenic belt in Nevada and Utah." From Geological Society of America Bulletin. (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Arnett, M.W. and Mamatey, A.R. eds. "Savannah River site, environmental data for 1999: WSRC-TR-99-00301 [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Arnett, M.W. and Mamatey, A.R. eds. "Savannah River site, environmental data for 1999: WSCR-TR-99-00299 [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 11)
- American Society of Mechanical Engineers. "1995 ASME boiler and pressure vessel code section III: Rules for construction of nuclear power plant components division 1 - subsection NB class 1 components." (Box 87, Folder 12)
- American Society of Mechanical Engineers. "1998 ASME boiler and pressure vessel code [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 13)
- American Society for Testing and Materials. "Standard specification for low-carbon nickel-molybdenum-chromium, low-carbon nickel-chromium-molybdenum, low-carbon nickel-chromium-molybdenum-copper and low-carbon nickel-chromium-molybdenum-tungsten alloy plate, sheet, and strip." ASTM B 575-97. (Box 87, Folder 14)
- American Society for Testing and Materials. "Standard practice for prediction of the long-term behavior of materials, including waste forms, used in engineered barrier systems (EBS) for geological disposal of high-level radioactive waste." (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Babula, J. "New hospital stimulates senses, St. Rose Dominican Hospital's Siena campus in Henderson will offer a gardenlike atmosphere." From Las Vegas Review-Journal. (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Baker, D.L., Arnold, M.E. and Scott, H.D. "Some analytical and approximate Darcian means." From Ground Water. (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Baron, J., Hershey, J.C., Kunreuther, H. "Determinants of priority for risk reduction: The role of worry." From Risk Analysis. (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Baxter, P. "[Email page with a spreadsheet plot roll: 2000 rad survey popgrid. Email communication to von Reis, J., Jason Technologies]." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Bureau of Economic Analysis. "Regional economic information service data: Bureau of Economic Analysis Clark County 1969-96." (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Bell, M.J. "[Issue resolution status report on 'methodology to assess fault displacement and vibratory ground motion hazard at Yucca Mountain. Letter to Dr. S. Brocoum, DOE]." U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. (Box 87, Folder 21)
- The Louis Berger Group, Inc. "Assessment of the hazards of transporting spent nuclear fuel and high level radioactive waste to the proposed Yucca Mountain repository using the proposed Northern Las Vegas beltway [document removed]." (Box 87, Folder 22)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Summary of round table discussion on issues for assessing risks of spent nuclear fuel transportation accidents public meeting, November 17, 1999 - Bethesda, Maryland." (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Best, R. "[Waste generated during the maintenance of locomotive. Telephone log of conversation with R. Lewis, Southern Freight Logistics]." Jason Technologies, Inc. (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Biasi, G.P. "Teleseismic tomographic imaging of the Yucca Mountain region." University of Nevada, Reno. (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Biwer, B.M. and Butler, J.P. "Vehicle emission unit risk factors for transportation risk assessments." From Risk Analysis. (Box 88, Folder 4)
- U.S. Bureau of Land Management. "Proposed resource management plan and final environmental impact statement for the Shoshone-Eureka resource area Nevada, table of contents and summary." INT FEIS 84-02. (Box 88, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of the Interior, Bureau of Land Management, Battle Mountain Field Office. "Record of decision and plan of operations approval: Cortez Gold Mines south pipeline project." (Box 88, Folder 6)
- U.S. Bureau of Land Management. "Round 2 preliminary recommendation, expenditure of the special account." (Box 88, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of the Interior, Bureau of Land Management, Battle Mountain Field Office. "South pipeline project final environmental impact statement." NV64-93-001P(96-2A) NV063-EIS98-014. (Box 88, Folder 8)
- U.S. Bureau of Land Management. "1998 program planning, current projects." (Box 88, Folder 9)
- U.S. Bureau of Land Management. "Draft Nevada test & training range resource management plan and environmental impact statement." (Box 88, Folder 10)
- U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. "Fatal workplace injuries in 1998 and 1999: A collection of data and analysis." Report 954. (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Blythe, R.A., Hart, J.D., Miles, J.C. et al. "The central electricity generating board flask test project." From the Proceedings of an International Symposium on the Packaging and Transportation of Radioactive Materials 1986. (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Bodvarsson, G.S. and Bandurraga, T.M. eds. "Development and calibration of the three-dimensional site-scale unsaturated zone model of Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Ernest Orlando Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory. (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Boice, J. Jr. "Studies of atomic bomb survivors: Understanding radiation effects [document missing]." (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Bowen, S.M., Finnegan, D.L., Thompson, J.L. et al. "Nevada test site radionuclide inventory 1951-1992." Los Alamos National Laboratory. LA-13859-MS. (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Bowman, C.D. and Venneri, F. "Underground autocatalytic criticality from plutonium and other fissile material." Los Alamos National Laboratory. LA-UR-94-4022. (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Brenot, J., Bonnefous, S. and Marris, C. "Testing the cultural theory of risk in France." From Risk Analysis. (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Brocoum, S. "[Biological assessment of the effects of construction, operation and monitoring, and closure of a geologic repository at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Letter to R.D. Williams, Department of the Interior]." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Brussard, P.F., Berry, K.H., Gilpin, M.E. et al. "Desert tortoise (Mojave population) recovery plan." U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service. (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Ahlers, C.F. "Unsaturated zone flow patterns and analysis." MDL-NBS-HS-000012 REV 00. (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Williams, N.H. "Total systems performance assessment - analysis for disposal of commercial and DOE waste inventories at Yucca Mountain - input to final environmental impact statement and site suitability evaluation." Revision 00 ICN 02. (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Concept of operations for waste transport, emplacement, and retrieval [document removed]." (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "OUO consequence of an aircraft crash into a transportation cask." (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Calculation: Consumption rates of locally produced food in Nye and Lincoln Counties." CAL-MGR-EV-000002 REV 00. (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Features, events and processes in UZ flow and transport." ANL-NBS-MD-000001 REV 01. (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "FY 01 supplemental science and performance analyses, volume 1: Scientific bases and analyses." TDR-MGR-MD-000007 REV 00 ICN 01. (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "FY 01 supplemental science and performance analyses, volume 2: Performance analyses." TDR-MGR-PA-000001 REV 00. (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Gantry structural/control system analysis [document removed]." (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Inventory abstraction." ANL-WIS-MD-000006 REV 00 ICN 02." (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Performance assessment of U.S. Department of Energy spent fuels in support of site recommendation." CAL-WIS-PA-000002 REV 00. (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Saturated zone flow patterns and analysis." ANL-NBS-HS-000038 REV 00A. (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Saturated zone transport-time analyses letter report." MIS-MGR-HS-000001 REV 00. (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Software code: GoldSim [document removed]." (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Technical update impact letter report." MIS-MGR-RL-000001 REV 00 ICN 02. (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Waste package radionuclide inventory approximations for TSPA-SR." CAL-WIS-MD-000004 REV 00 ICN 01. (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Bechtel SAIC Company. "Lower-temperature subsurface layout and ventilation concepts [document removed]." (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Budnitz, B., Ewing, R.C., Moeller, D.W. et al. "Peer review of the total system performance assessment-viability assessment final report." (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Bureau of the Census. "National population projections I: Summary files." (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Bureau of the Census. "Census 2000 redistricting data [compact disc]." P.L. 94-171. (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Bureau of the Census. "Statistical abstract of the United States 2000." (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Bureau of the Census. "Profiles of general demographic characteristics: 2000 census of population and housing-Nevada." (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Bureau of the Census. "Overview of race and Hispanic origin." (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Burger, J., Sanchez, J., Gibbons, J et al. "Risk perception, federal spending, and the Savannah River site: Attitudes of hunters and fishermen." From Risk Analysis. (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Bush, C.A., Bunker, C.M. and Spengler, R.W. "Radioelement distribution in drill-hole USW-G1, Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada." Open file report 83-847. (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Carl, B. "[Request from EIS folks. Email communication to T. Ikenberry, Dade Moeller and Associates]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Cember, H. "Introduction to health physics, 2nd edition [document removed]." (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Council on Environmental Quality. "Incorporating biodiversity considerations into environmental impact analysis under the National Environmental Policy Act." (Box 91, Folder 9)
- National Energy Policy Development Group. "National energy policy." (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Chanin, D.I. and Murfin, W.B. "Site restoration: Estimation of attributable costs from plutonium-dispersal accidents." Technadyne Engineering Consultants, Inc and Sandia National Laboratories. SAND96-0957. (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Chess, C. 2001. "Organizational theory and the stages of risk communication." From Risk Analysis. (Box 91, Folder 12)
- City of Las Vegas. "Las Vegas 2020 City of Las Vegas master plan." (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Claassen, H.C. "Sources and mechanisms of recharge for ground water in the west-central Amargosa Desert, Nevada - a geochemical interpretation." U.S. Geological Survey professional paper 712-F. (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area." (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area. Appendix A: Emissions inventory." (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area. Appendix B: Transport documentation." (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area. Appendix C: Modeling documentation." (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area. Appendix D: Regulations, policies and public participation documentation." (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Clark County. "Carbon monoxide state implementation plan Las Vegas Valley nonattainment area. Appendix E: Supplemental technical support documentation." (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Crowe, B.M. "[Subcritical experiments. Email to E. Rollins, Dade Moeller and Associates]." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Clark County. "Particulate matter (PM-10) state implementation plan." (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Cohen, B.L. "Catalog of risks extended and updated." From Health Physics. (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Crowley, K.D. "Statement of Kevin D. Crowley, Ph.D. Director, Board on Radioactive Waste Management, National Research Council, concerning Yucca Mountain radiation protection standards." National Academy of Sciences. (Box 93, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Distribution of natural and man-made radionuclides in soil and biota at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." REV 00. (Box 93, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - viability assessment (TSPA-VA) plan." B00000000-01717-2200-00179. (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Geomatrix Consultants, Inc and TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Probabilistic volcanic hazard analysis for Yucca Mountain, Nevada." BA0000000-01717-2200-00082, Rev 0. (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Intermodal transfer site, apex/dry lake siting area map." BCBI00000-01717-2700-82039 REV 00. (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Intermodal transfer site, Jean siting area map." BCBI00000-01717-2700-82041 REV 00." (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Intermodal transfer site, Sloan siting area map." BCBI00000-01717-2700-82040 REV 00." (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Rail alignment design, Carlin route Crescent Valley section, Plate 1." BCBI00000-01717-2700-82003 REV 00. (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Rail alignments analysis." BCBI00000-01717-0200-00002 REV 00. (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Secondary waste treatment analysis." BCBD00000-01717-0200-00005 REV00. (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Sensitive species confirmation surveys." (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Broad based risk analysis subsurface facilities [document removed]." (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Economic analysis of at-reactor dry storage for the no-action alternative [document removed]." (Box 94, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "The effects of site characterization activities on the abundance of ravens (Corvus corax) in the Yucca Mountain area." B00000000-01717-5705-00040. (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Emplacement drift isolation door control system." (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Nevada transportation study construction cost estimate [document removed]." (Box 94, Folder 8)